A Guide to the City College of New York collection of the Russell Sage Foundation Library FA1208
Rockefeller Archive Center
City College of New York collection of the Russell Sage Foundation Library
1838-2009
Rockefeller Archive Center
City University of New York. City College
Russell Sage Foundation
FA1208
135.69 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
Original order, as received.
Scope and Contents
Collection consists of reports, studies, field reports, conference and workshop papers, annual reports, yearbooks, financial statements, and budgets collected by the Russell Sage Foundation library.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated to RAC as an unrestricted gift by City College of New York in 2018.
Custodial History
The contents of this collection was originally transferred to the City College of New York directly from Russell Sage Foundation. RAC then received the holdings from CCNY.
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1927-1928 (Box 1)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1923-1924 (Box 1)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1921-1922 (Box 1)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1919-1920 (Box 1)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1917-1918 (Box 1)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1915 (Box 1)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1939-1940 (Box 1A)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1935-1936 (Box 1A)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1931-1932 (Box 1A)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1925-1926 (Box 1A)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1929-1930 (Box 1A)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1937-1938 (Box 2)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1952 (Box 2)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1953 (Box 2)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1954 (Box 2)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1955 (Box 2)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1956 (Box 2)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1957 (Box 2)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1958 (Box 2)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1959 (Box 2)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1960 (Box 2)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1961 (Box 2)
- Rockefeller Foundation Annual Report, 1962 (Box 2)
- Occasional Papers 1-3, 1925-1927 (Box 2A)
- Occasional Papers 4-5, 1928-1930 (Box 2A)
- The Pilgrim Trust First Annual Report 1-4, 1939 (Box 2A)
- The Pilgrim Trust Fifth Annual Report 5-8, 1939 (Box 2A)
- The Pilgrim Trust Ninth Annual Report 9-15, 1939 (Box 2A)
- King Edward's Hospital Fund, 1900-1909 (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1951 January (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1951 February (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1951 March (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1951 April (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1951 May (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1951 June (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1951 July (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1951 August (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1951 September (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1951 October (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1951 November (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1951 December (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1952 January (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1952 February (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1952 March (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1952 April (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1952 May (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1952 June (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1952 July (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1952 August (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1952 September (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1952 October (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1952 November (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1952 December (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1953 January (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1953 February (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1953 March (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1953 April (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1953 May (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1953 June (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1953 July (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1953 August (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1953 September (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1953 October (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1953 November (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1953 December (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1954 January (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1954 February (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1954 March (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1954 April (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1954 May (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1954 June (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1954 July (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1954 August (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1954 September (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1955 January (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1955 February (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1955 March (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1955 April (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1955 May (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1955 June (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1955 July (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1955 August (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1955 September (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1955 October (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1955 November (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1955 December (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, January 1956 (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1956 February (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1956 March (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1956 April (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1956 May (Box 2A)
- The Volunteer: Gazette- Voice of the Volunteers of America, 1956 June (Box 2A)
- Index to Volume I and Volume II, 1942 November - 1944 December (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 2 Number 2, 1944 January (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 2 Number 3, 1944 February (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 2 Number 4, 1944 March (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 2 Number 5, 1944 April (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 2 Number 6, 1944 May (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 2 Number 7, 1944 June (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 2 Number 8, 1944 July (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 2 Number 9, 1944 September (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 2 Number 10, 1944 October (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 2 Number 11, 1944 November (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 2 Number 12, 1944 December (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 3 Number 1, 1945 January (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 3 Number 2, 1945 February - March (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 3 Number 4, 1945 April (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 3 Number 5, 1945 May (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 3 Number 6, 1945 June (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 3 Number 7, 1945 September (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 3 Number 8, 1945 October (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 3 Number 9, 1945 December (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 4 Number 1, 1946 January (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 4 Number 2, 1946 February-March (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 4 Number 3, 1946 April (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 4 Number 4, 1946 May-June (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 4 Number 5, 1946 July-August (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 4 Number 6, 1946 October (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 4 Number 7, 1946 November (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 4 Number 8, 1946 December (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 5 Number 1, 1947 January (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 5 Number 2, 1947 February-March (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 5 Number 3, 1947 April (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 5 Number 4, 1947 May (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 5 Number 5, 1947 July-August (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 5 Number 6, 1947 September (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 5 Number 7, 1947 October-November (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 5 Number 8, 1947 December (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 6 Number 1, 1948 January (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 6 Number 2, 1948 February-March (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 6 Number 3, 1948 April (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 6 Number 4, 1948 May (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 6 Number 5, 1948 July (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 6 Number 6, 1948 October (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 6 Number 7, 1948 November (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 6 Number 8, 1948 December (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 6 Number 9, 1949 January (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 7 Number 2, 1949 March (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 7 Number 3, 1949 April (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 7 Number 4, 1949 May (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 7 Number 5, 1949 July (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 7 Number 6, 1949 October (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 7 Number 7, 1949 November (Box 3)
- Counseling Volume 7 Number 8, 1949 December (Box 3)
- New Cross Afire in Dixie by James Desmond, 1905 May (Box 3)
- Bulletin of Family Research and Education Vol. I No. 1 - Vol. II Nos. 5-6, 1940-1941 (Box 3)
- The Hundred-year Book: A synoptic Review of Association History: The Centennial Issue of the YMCA Year Book for 1943 (Box 3)
- YMCA Year Book and Official Rosters, 1934 (Box 3)
- YMCA Year Book and Official Rosters, 1935 (Box 3)
- YMCA Year Book and Official Rosters, 1936 (Box 3)
- YMCA Year Book and Official Roster for the Calendar Year 1936 (Box 3)
- YMCA Year Book and Official Roster for the Calendar Year 1937 (Box 3)
- YMCA Year Book and Official Roster for the Calendar Year 1938 (Box 3)
- YMCA Year Book and Official Roster for the Calendar Year 1939 (Box 3)
- YMCA Year Book and Official Roster for the Calendar Year 1940 (Box 3)
- YMCA Year Book and Official Roster for the Calendar Year 1941 (Box 3)
- YMCA Year Book and Official Roster for the Calendar Year 1942 (Box 3)
- YMCA Year Book and Official Roster for the Calendar Year 1944 (Box 3)
- YMCA Year Book and Official Roster for the Calendar Year 1947 (Box 3)
- Selected Bibliography on the Negro (x2 Copies), 1951 (Box 4)
- Great Britain. Report from Standing Committee A on the National Health Insurance Bill with the Proceedings of the Committee, 1916 December (Box 4)
- Great Britain. National Health Insurance. Notes Explanatory of the National Health Insurance Bill, 1917 Report from Standing Committee A on the National Helath Insurance Bill with the Proceedings of the Committee (Box 4)
- Great Britain. Inter-departmental Committee on Insurance Medical Records, 1920 (Box 4)
- Annual Report, 1914-1920 (Box 4)
- Year book of the (Collegiate) Reformed Protestant Dutch Church of the City of New York, 1958 (Box 4)
- Year book of the (Collegiate) Reformed Protestant Dutch Church of the City of New York, 1959 (Box 4)
- Year book of the (Collegiate) Reformed Protestant Dutch Church of the City of New York, 1960 (Box 4)
- Year book of the (Collegiate) Reformed Protestant Dutch Church of the City of New York, 1961 (Box 4)
- Year book of the (Collegiate) Reformed Protestant Dutch Church of the City of New York, 1962 (Box 4)
- Year book of the (Collegiate) Reformed Protestant Dutch Church of the City of New York, 1963 (Box 4)
- Year book of the (Collegiate) Reformed Protestant Dutch Church of the City of New York, 1964 (Box 4)
- Year book of the (Collegiate) Reformed Protestant Dutch Church of the City of New York, 1965 (Box 4)
- Year book of the (Collegiate) Reformed Protestant Dutch Church of the City of New York, 1966 (Box 4)
- Year book of the (Collegiate) Reformed Protestant Dutch Church of the City of New York, 1967 (Box 4)
- Year book of the (Collegiate) Reformed Protestant Dutch Church of the City of New York, 1968 (Box 4)
- Year book of the (Collegiate) Reformed Protestant Dutch Church of the City of New York, 1969 (Box 4)
- Year book of the (Collegiate) Reformed Protestant Dutch Church of the City of New York, 1970 (Box 4)
- Consumer Credit Charges After the War No. 46, 1944 (Box 5)
- Damming and Diversion of Consumer Credit No. 45, 1944 (Box 5)
- Consumer Credit Controls No. 42, 1944 (Box 5)
- Consumer Loans By Commercial Banks No. 40, 1944 (Box 5)
- How Easy Are "Easy Payments"? No. 39, 1944 (Box 5)
- Pollak Pamphlet No. 41, 1944 (Box 5)
- Small Loan Laws of the United States No. 37, 1944 (Box 5)
- One Hundred Problems In Consumer Credit No. 35, 1944 (Box 5)
- State Regulations of Installment Selling and Financing No. 30, 1944 (Box 5)
- Can Consumers Stand ithe Truth? No. 27, 1944 (Box 5)
- Painless Debtistry No. 22, 1944 (Box 5)
- The League From Year To Year, 1937 (Box 5)
- Youth and Jobs in Canada, 1945 (Box 5)
- Youth Canada and Religion, 1945 (Box 5)
- Annual report of President and auditor, 1955 (Box 5)
- Annual report of President and auditor, 1956 (Box 5)
- Annual report of President and auditor, 1957 (Box 5)
- Annual report of President and auditor, 1958 (Box 5)
- Annual report of President and auditor, 1959 (Box 5)
- Annual report of President and auditor, 1960 (Box 5)
- Annual report of President and auditor, 1961 (Box 5)
- Annual report of President and auditor, 1962 (Box 5)
- Annual report of President and auditor, 1963 (Box 5)
- Annual report of President and auditor, 1964 (Box 5)
- Annual report of President and auditor, 1965 (Box 5)
- Annual report of President and auditor, 1966 (Box 5)
- Annual report of President and auditor, 1967 (Box 5)
- Annual report of President and auditor, 1968 (Box 5)
- The Economic and social council an Instrument of Int'l Cooperation (Box 5)
- International Organization for Health, 1944 (Box 5)
- Proposals for the United Nations charter, 1944 (Box 5)
- The United nations and non-self governing peoples, 1944 (Box 5)
- A Layman's Program for Peace, 1943 (Box 5)
- Third report - The United nations and the organization of peace;with papers presented to the commission., 1943 (Box 5)
- Fundamentals of the international organization: Fourth Report, 1943-1944 (Box 5)
- Fourth Report: Part I. Security and world organization, 1943 (Box 5)
- Fourth Report: Part II. The economic organization of welfare, 1943 (Box 5)
- Toward greater freedom: Problems of War and Peace, 1942 (Box 5)
- Guide to community activity on human rights., 1946 (Box 5)
- Arbitration in international controversy, 1944 (Box 5)
- Technical Assistance for Economic Development program of the united nations and the specialized agencies, 1950 (Box 5)
- Preliminary report and monographs., 1942 (Box 5)
- Security and disarmament under the United Nations: fifth report., 1947 (Box 5)
- Second report the transitional period, 1942 (Box 5)
- Collective self-defense under the United Nations: memorandum and draft treaty for implementation of Article 51., 1948 (Box 5)
- Geneva as a center of economic information, 1934 (Box 5)
- The United Nations at work: basic documents., 1947 (Box 5)
- The International Opium Conferences With Relevant Documents., 1925 (Box 5)
- Publications 1950, 1946-1948 (Box 5)
- Current Publications on International Affairs, 1948 (Box 5)
- World peace Foundation, 1910 (Box 5)
- Report on the work of the League during the war, submitted to the Assembly by the acting Secretary-General, 1945 (Box 5)
- Report on the work of the League: Part I, 1937-1938 (Box 5)
- Report on the work of the League: Part II, 1937-1938 (Box 5)
- Report on the work of the League 1943-1944, 1945 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1924 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1925 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1926 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1927 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1929 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1935 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1936 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1937 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1938 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1939 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1940 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1941 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1942 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1943 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1944 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1945 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1946 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1947 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1948 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1949 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1950 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1951 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1952 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1953 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors, 1954 (Box 5)
- The Church Peace Union: Report of the secretaries and the auditors (Box 5)
- The Volunteer, 1970 March (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1970 April (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1970 May (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1970 June (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1970 July (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1970 August (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1970 October (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1970 November (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1970 December (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1971 January (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1971 February (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1971 March (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1971 April (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1971 May (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1971 June (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1971 July (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1971 September (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1971 October (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1971 November (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1971 December (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1972 January (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1972 February (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1972 March (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1972 April (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1972 May (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1972 June (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1972 July (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1972 August (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1972 September (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1972 December (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1973 January (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1973 April (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1973 May (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1973 June (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1973 July (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1973 August (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1973 October (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1973 November (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1973 December (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1974 January (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1974 April (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1974 November (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1975 January (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1975 March (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1975 July (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1975 August (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1975 September (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1975 October (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1975 November (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1975 December (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1976 January (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1976 February (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1976 March (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1976 April (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1976 May (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1976 June (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1976 July (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1976 August (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1976 September (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1976 October (Box 5A)
- The Volunteer, 1976 November (Box 5A)
- Family Life (25 Issues), 1947 November - 1949 November (Box 5A)
- Family Life (11 Issues), 1950 May - 1951 March (Box 5A)
- Family Life, 1951 June (Box 5A)
- Family Life (8 Issues), 1951 December - 1952 July (Box 5A)
- Family Life (3 Issues), 1952 October - December (Box 5A)
- Family Life (25 Issues), 1953 January - 1955 January (Box 5A)
- Family Life (26 Issues), 1955 February - 1957 March (Box 5A)
- Wages,Earnings, and Hours of Work 1914-1947, United Kingdom (Box 6)
- National Bureau Annual Report (15 Issues), 1930-1945 (Box 6)
- National Bureau Annual Report (2 copies), 1947 (Box 6)
- National Bureau Annual Report, 1951-1952 (Box 6)
- Wages in various industries and occupations, a summary of wage movements, 1914-1920 No. 8 (Box 6)
- Standards of living, a compilation of budgetary studies No. 7, 1920-1932 (Box 6)
- Standards of living, a compilation of budgetary studies No. 5, 1919 (Box 6)
- Changes in Cost of Living and Prices, 1914-1920 (Box 6)
- Wages in various industries. A summary of wage movements during the war, 1919 (Box 6)
- Changes in cost of living 1914-1919, a summary of existing data (Box 6)
- Royal Economic Society No. 91-108, 1942-1946 (Box 6)
- Royal Economic Society No. 51-60, 1935-1936 (Box 6)
- Royal Economic Society No. 21, 1930-1931 (Box 6)
- Royal Economic Society No. 1-10, 1927 (Box 6)
- Royal Economic Society No. 11-20, 1929-1930 (Box 6)
- Royal Economic Society No. 61-70, 1936-1938 (Box 6)
- Royal Economic Society No. 31-40, 1931-1933 (Box 6)
- Royal Economic Society No. 41-50, 1933-1934 (Box 6)
- Royal Economic Society No. 81-90, 1940 (Box 6)
- Research on Aging: Proceedings of a Conference Held on August 7-10, 1950, at the University of California, Berkeley (Box 7)
- Housing and Post-war Planning in England and America by Luther Gulick, 1941 (Box 7)
- Housing and Post-war Planning in England and America by Luther Gulick, 1941 (Box 7)
- Local Taxation and Housing, 1939 (Box 7)
- Wartime Housing in the New York Metropolitan Area, 1942 (Box 7)
- London County (England). Council School Dentistry in Germany, 1910 (Box 7)
- A Program for Community Districts, 1964 (Box 7)
- Ailing City Areas Economic Study of Thirteen Depressed Districts in Manhattan, 1941 (Box 7)
- Rents in Public Housing A discussion of Their Advantages and disadvantages, with Fourteen Plans, Proposed or in Operation, 1941 (Box 7)
- The Relation of Tax Delinquency in Slum Areas to the Housing Problem, 1942 (Box 7)